Guide to the Stanford University, Commission of Engineers, Records
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Commission of Engineers, records
1906-1908
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Commission of Engineers
SC0001
2.5 Linear Feet (13 boxes)
The records of the Commission of Engineers, dating from 1906 to 1908, include correspondence, daily journal, estimates of repairs, reports, photographs, and negatives.
Biographical / Historical
The Commission of Engineers was charged with directing the restoration of the university's buildings after the earthquake of April 1906. The Commission, composed of Professors Charles D. Marx (civil engineering), Charles B. Wing (structural engineering), and William F. Durand (mechanical engineering), was appointed by the Board of Trustees in June 1906.
Scope and Contents
Records of the University's Commission of Engineers responsible for the reconstruction of Stanford University buildings after the 1906 earthquake. Includes correspondence, the Commission's daily journals, photographs, negatives, and estimates of repairs.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in SC 27 (Board of Trustees Supporting Documents), Box 1, folder for August 1, 1906, and in SC 28 (Horace Davis papers), Box 5, folder 37.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Administrative transfer, 1965.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Commission of Engineers was charged with directing the restoration of the university's buildings after the earthquake of April 1906. The Commission, composed of Professors Charles D. Marx (civil engineering), Charles B. Wing (structural engineering), and William F. Durand (mechanical engineering), was appointed by the Board of Trustees in June 1906.
Photonegatives; San Francisco Earthquake and Fire, Calif., 1906; Photoprints.; Journals.; Stanford University. Commission of Engineers; Durand, William Frederick; Wing, Charles B.; Marx, Charles David; Stanford University. Commission of Engineers
- Correspondence, 1906-1907
  - Correspondence of the Commission of Engineers, 1906-07 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of the Commission of Engineers, 1906-07 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence of the Commission of Engineers, 1906-07 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence of the Commission of Engineers, 1906-07 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence of the Commission of Engineers, 1906-07 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence of the Commission of Engineers, 1906-07 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence of the Commission of Engineers, 1906-07 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of the Commission of Engineers, 1906-07 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence of the Commission of Engineers, 1906-07 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence of the Commission of Engineers, 1906-07 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Photographs
  - Photographs of reconstruction (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of reconstruction (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of reconstruction (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of reconstruction (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of reconstruction (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of reconstruction (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photographs to accompany the Report of the Commission of Engineers to the Board of Trustees, 1906-07 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photographs to accompany the Report of the Commission of Engineers to the Board of Trustees, 1907-08 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Negatives of earthquake damage and reconstruction
    - Business office, south arcade [Negative# 1-1], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Small physics building, west side [Negative# 1-4], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Arcade between physics buildings [Negative# 1-5], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Arcade between physics buildings, W. center arch [Negative# 1-6], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Small physics buildings, south arcade [Negative# 1-7], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Arcade, inner quad, east of Church [Negative# 1-11], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Original envelope listing for set 1, 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Romantic language building, south arcade [Negative# 2-4], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Old library, east wall, s.e corner [Negative# 2-5], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - History and English buildings, flue [Negative# 2-6], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Physiology building [Negative# 2-7], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Memorial Arch from Memorial Court [Negative# 2-8], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Zoology building, chimney at s.e. corner [Negative# 2-9], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Zoology building, steam pipe [Negative# 2-10], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Memorial Church, west side [Negative# 2-12], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Original envelope listing for set 2, 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Romantic languages building, n. end e. arch [Negative# 3-1], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Romantic languages building, s. end e. arch [Negative# 3-2], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Business office, w. end n. arcade [Negative# 3-3], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Business office, e. end n. arcade [Negative# 3-4], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Business office, n. end e. arcade [Negative# 3-5], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Business office, center e. arcade [Negative# 3-6], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Business office, s. end e. arcade [Negative# 3-7], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Business office, s.e. corner [Negative# 3-8], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Boiler house, north side [Negative# 3-9], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Memorial Church, s.e. corner [Negative# 3-10], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Original envelope listing for set 3 (Box 6)
    - Mineralogy building, arcade [Negative# 4-2], Undated (Box 6)
    - Mineralogy building, arcade [Negative# 4-3], Undated (Box 6)
    - Small physics building, arcade [Negative# 4-4], Undated (Box 6)
    - Small physics building, arcade [Negative# 4-5], Undated (Box 6)
    - Romantic languages building, arcade [Negative# 4-6], Undated (Box 6)
    - Memorial Church, arcade [Negative# 4-7], Undated (Box 6)
    - Memorial Church, arcade [Negative# 4-8], Undated (Box 6)
    - Mineralogy building, arcade [Negative# 4-9], Undated (Box 6)
    - Mineralogy building, arcade [Negative# 4-10], Undated (Box 6)
    - Small physics building, arcade [Negative# 4-11], Undated (Box 6)
    - Romantic language building, arcade [Negative# 4-12], Undated (Box 6)
    - Original envelope listing for set 4 (Box 6)
    - Business office west arcade [Negative# 5-1], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Business office east arcade [Negative# 5-2], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Assembly Hall, rear view [Negative# 5-3], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Physics building [Negative# 5-4], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Small physics building, north arcade [Negative# 5-6], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Mineralogy building, north arcade [Negative# 5-7], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Business office, s.e. corner [Negative# 5-8], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Assay Laboratory, front view [Negative# 5-9], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Assay Laboratory [Negative# 5-10], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Chemistry building, front [Negative# 5-11], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Arcade, History to English [Negative# 5-12], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Original envelope for set 5 (Box 6)
    - Arcade between History, English and Romantic Lang. [Negative# 6-1], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Encina Hall, rear west wing [Negative# 6-3], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Encina Hall, rear east wing [Negative# 6-4], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Memorial Church, rear view [Negative# 6-5], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Arts building, s.e. corner [Negative# 6-6], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Small civil engineering building, s.w. corner [Negative# 6-7], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Memorial Arch, rear view [Negative# 6-8], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Small physics building, s.w. corner [Negative# 6-9], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Arcade between Geology and Mining buildings [Negative# 6-10], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Mechanical laboratory, s.w. corner [Negative# 6-12], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Original envelope for set 6 (Box 6)
    - New library, from the s.w. [Negative# 7-1], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, from the s.w. [Negative# 7-2], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Encina Hall, chimney at rear [Negative# 7-3], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Arcade, English building to business office [Negative# 7-4], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Encina Hall, front [Negative# 7-5], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Mechanical Laboratory, front [Negative# 7-6], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Boiler house, n.e. corner [Negative# 7-7], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Romantic Languages building, north arcade [Negative# 7-8], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Memorial Arch, front view [Negative# 7-9], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Arcade, English building to business office [Negative# 7-10], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Business office, east arcade [Negative# 7-11], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Business office, arcade [Negative# 7-12], 1906 Sep (Box 6)
    - Original envelope listing for set 7 (Box 6)
    - Business office, east arcade [Negative# 8-1], 1906 Sep-Oct (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, basement s. wing [Negative# 8-3], 1906 Sep-Oct (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, s. handball court, s. wing [Negative# 8-4], 1906 Sep-Oct (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, n. handball court, s. wing [Negative# 8-6], 1906 Sep-Oct (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, north wing north wall [Negative# 8-7], 1906 Sep-Oct (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, interior court, rear [Negative# 8-9], 1906 Sep-Oct (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, east wall s. wing [Negative# 8-10], 1906 Sep-Oct (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, east wall n. wing [Negative# 8-11], 1906 Sep-Oct (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, south wall, s. wing [Negative# 8-12], 1906 Sep-Oct (Box 6)
    - Original envelope listing for set 8 (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, west wall of north wing [Negative# 9-1], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Gymnasium, west wall of south wing [Negative# 9-2], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Memorial Court, rear view [Negative# 9-3], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Boiler house, rear view of stack [Negative# 9-4], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Arcades, history & English to romantic languages [Negative# 9-5], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Memorial Church, front gable [Negative# 9-6], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Business office, e.c. arch south arcade [Negative# 9-7], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Business office, w.c. arch south arcade [Negative# 9-8], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Romantic languages building, e. arches south arcade [Negative# 9-9], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Romantic languages building, w. arches south arcade [Negative# 9-10], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Romantic languages building, e. c. arch south arcade [Negative# 9-11], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Memorial Church, rear view [Negative# 9-12], 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Original envelope listing for set 9, 1906 Oct (Box 6)
    - Mechanical lab, front entrance [Negative# 10-1], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Arcades between art and geology buildings [Negative# 10-2], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Memorial Court, name plate of west arcade [Negative# 10-3], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, front view [Negative# 10-4], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Arcades between physics buildings [Negative# 10-5], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Roble Hall, front view [Negative# 10-6], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Chemistry building, view of roof [Negative# 10-7], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Chemistry building, view of front steps [Negative# 10-8], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Chemistry building, front of Assay Lab [Negative# 10-9], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Romantic Languages building, north arcade [Negative# 10-11], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, rear view [Negative# 10-12], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Original envelope listing for set 10 (Box 7)
    - Memorial Church, front gable [Negative# 11-1], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Arcade, art building to geological building, north wall [Negative# 11-2], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Art building, s.w. corner [Negative# 11-3], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Physics building, s. arcade [Negative# 11-5], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Physics building, s. arcade [Negative# 11-6], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, west wall at base [Negative# 11-7], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, east wall at base [Negative# 11-8], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Original envelope listing for set 11, 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Encina Hall, rear wall west wing [Negative# 12-1], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Encina Hall, rear wall east wing [Negative# 12-2], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Chemistry building, rear of Assay Lab [Negative# 12-3], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Wall at left of gable of Assay Bldg. [Negative# 12-4], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Mining building, south arcade [Negative# 12-5], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Assembly Hall, front [Negative# 12-6], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, rear view [Negative# 12-7], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Small physics building, n. arcade [Negative# 12-8], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Arcades, history and English to romantic languages [Negative# 12-9], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Romantic languages building, east arcade [Negative# 12-10], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Gymnasium, n.w. corner [Negative# 12-11], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Gymnasium, wall of interior court [Negative# 12-12], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Original envelope listing for set 12, 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Business office, arcade [Negative# 13-1 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Romantic languages building, arcade [Negative# 13-2 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Small physics building, south arcade [Negative# 13-3 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Arcade, engineering building to business office [Negative# 13-4 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Physics building, arcade at rear [Negative# 13-5 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Museum, south end front facade [Negative# 13-6 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Museum, north end front facade [Negative# 13-7 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Museum, general view from s.w., [Negative# 13-8 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Small physics building, w. and s. arcade [Negative# 13-10 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Mineralogy building, n. and w. arcade [Negative# 13-11 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, rear view [Negative# 13-12 ], 1906 Oct (Box 7)
    - Original envelope listing for set 13 (Box 7)
    - Mechanical Lab, s.w. corner [Negative# 14-1 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Boiler house, rear view [Negative# 14-2], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Woodworking shop, from the s.w. [Negative# 14-3 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Blacksmith shop, north wall [Negative# 14-4 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Small physics building, c. arch to physics building [Negative# 14-5 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Encina Hall, west wing west side [Negative# 14-6 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Encina Hall, west wing east side [Negative# 14-7], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Encina Hall, east wing west side [Negative# 14-8 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Encina Hall, east wing east side [Negative# 14-9 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - New Library from Encina Hall [Negative# 14-10 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Chemistry building, rear view from s.w. [Negative# 14-11 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, front view [Negative# 14-12], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Original envelope listing for set 14 (Box 7)
    - Engineering building to business office, west wall [Negative# 15-2 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, rear view [Negative# 15-3], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Physiology building, arcade [Negative# 15-4], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, rear view [Negative# 15-5 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Arcade, physiology bldg. to Memorial Arch, east wall [Negative# 15-6 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Arcade, Assembly Hall to Memorial Arch, east wall [Negative# 15-7 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Arcade, Assembly Hall to Memorial Arch, west wall [Negative# 15-8 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Mining building, arcade to geology building [Negative# 15-9 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Mining building, n. arcade to w.c. arch [Negative# 15-10 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Mineralogy building, arcade to e.c. arch [Negative# 15-11 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, rear view [Negative# 15-12 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Original envelope listing for set 15 (Box 7)
    - Arcade, Romantic Languages to History & English building, east wall [Negative# 16-1 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Encina Hall, rear of west wing [Negative# 16-2 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Encina Hall, rear of east wing [Negative# 16-3 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Chemistry building, s.w. corner [Negative# 16-4 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Romantic Languages to History & English building, west wall [Negative# 16-5 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Arcade, Romantic Languages to History & English building, brace frame between gables [Negative# 16-6 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - History & English building, cross arch to Romantic Languages building [Negative# 16-7 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, front view [Negative# 16-8 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Memorial Arch, view from Univ. Avenue [Negative# 16-9 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Arcade, law building to President's office, north wall [Negative# 16-10 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Arcade, law building to President's office [Negative# 16-11 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Arcade, law building to President's office [Negative# 16-12 ], 1906 Nov (Box 7)
    - Original envelope listing for set 16 (Box 7)
    - Arcades, law bldg. to admin. bldg., south wall [Negative# 17-1 ], 1906 Dec (Box 7)
    - Arcades, law bldg. to admin. bldg., south wall, elevation of arches [Negative# 17-2 ], 1906 Dec (Box 7)
    - Arcades, law bldg. to admin. bldg., north wall [Negative# 17-3 ], 1906 Dec (Box 7)
    - Arcades, law bldg. to admin. bldg., chain blocks and counter weights [Negative# 17-4], 1906 Dec (Box 7)
    - Arcades, law bldg. to admin. bldg., supporting cable at porch [Negative# 17-5 ], 1906 Dec (Box 7)
    - Arcades, law bldg. to admin. bldg., showing timbers and rollers [Negative# 17-6], 1906 Dec (Box 7)
    - Arcades, law bldg. to admin. bldg., showing timbers and rollers [Negative# 17-7 ], 1906 Dec (Box 7)
    - Arcades, law bldg. to admin. bldg., showing rear cables for checking [Negative# 17-8], 1906 Dec (Box 7)
    - Arcades, law bldg. to admin. bldg., showing rear cables for checking [Negative# 17-9], 1906 Dec (Box 7)
    - Memorial Church, front view [Negative# 17-12 ], 1906 Dec (Box 7)
    - Original envelope listing for set 17 (Box 7)
    - Small civil engineering building, s.w. corner [Negative# 18-1], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Arcade [ceiling], English building to business office [Negative# 18-2], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Engineering building cross arch to business office [Negative# 18-3 ], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Arcade, engineering building to business office, east wall [Negative# 18-4 ], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Arcade, engineering building to business office, west wall [Negative# 18-5 ], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - History & English building, s.w. walls [Negative# 18-6], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Gymnasium, south side from library [Negative# 18-7 ], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Gymnasium, west side [Negative# 18-8 ], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Chemistry building, n.e. corner [Negative# 18-9 ], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Chemistry building, n.w. corner [Negative# 18-10 ], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Chemistry building, n.w. corner [Negative# 18-11], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Chemistry building, s.w. corner [Negative# 18-12 ], 1906 Dec - 1907 Jan (Box 7)
    - Original envelope listing for set 18 (Box 7)
    - Boiler house, front elevation [Negative# 19-1 ], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Mechanical lab, front view [Negative# 19-2], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Art building, s.e. corner [Negative# 19-3 ], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Mineralogy building, north arcade [Negative# 19-4 ], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Arcade [ceilings], physics building [Negative# 19-5 ], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Physics building, cross Arch to small physics building [Negative# 19-6 ], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Arcade, physics building to small physics building [Negative# 19-7], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Arcade, physics building to small physics building, west wall [Negative# 19-9 ], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Arcade, physics building to small physics building, west wall of Main Arch [Negative# 19-10 ], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Arcades, Memorial Arch to Physics Building [Negative# 19-11 ], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Arcades, Memorial Arch to Assembly Hall [Negative# 19-12 ], 1907 Jan (Box 8)
    - Original envelope listing for set 19 (Box 8)
    - History and English buildings, s.w. elevation [Negative# 20-1 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - Arcades, law to admin. building [Negative# 20-2 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - Memorial Arch, view from Memorial Court [Negative# 20-3 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - Arcades, east side Memorial Court [Negative# 20-4 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - Memorial Arch, view from front [Negative# 20-5 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, rear center [Negative# 20-6 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, n. wing, n.e. corner [Negative# 20-7 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - Surface drainage, mech. engineering lab [Negative# 20-8 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - History and English buildings, s.w. elevation [Negative# 20-10 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - History and English buildings, details [Negative# 20-11 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - History and English buildings, details [Negative# 20-12 ], 1907 Jan-Feb (Box 8)
    - Original envelope listing for set 20 (Box 8)
    - Assembly Hall, w. rear exit stairway [Negative# 21-1 ], 1907 Feb (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, rear center [Negative# 21-6 ], 1907 Feb (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, gate at rear entrance [Negative# 21-7 ], 1907 Feb (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, gate at rear entrance [Negative# 21-8 ], 1907 Feb (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, rear center [Negative# 21-9 ], 1907 Feb (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, north end [Negative# 21-10 ], 1907 Feb (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, n. wall of east face [Negative# 21-11 ], 1907 Feb (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, n. wall of east face [Negative# 21-12 ], 1907 Feb (Box 8)
    - Original envelope listing for set 21 (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, int. wall, n. hall, 2nd floor [Negative# 22-1 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, reinforcement of roof in attic [Negative# 22-2 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, reinforcement of roof in attic [Negative# 22-3 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, stack of Assay Lab [Negative# 22-4 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - [copies of pre-earthquake photos] [Negative# 22-5 ] (Box 8)
    - Assembly Hall, east rear exit [Negative# 22-6 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Memorial Arch, from Memorial Court [Negative# 22-7 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, int. wall, n. hall, 1st floor [Negative# 22-8 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, int. wall, n. hall, 2nd floor [Negative# 22-9 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, int. wall, n. hall, 1st floor [Negative# 22-10 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, north portion of east front [Negative# 22-11], Undated (Box 8)
    - Chemistry building, east front of s. wing [Negative# 22-12], Undated (Box 8)
    - Original envelope listing for set 22 (Box 8)
    - Surface drainage, alley back of S.K. house [Negative# 23-2 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Surface drainage, intake near Cooksey gate [Negative# 23-3 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Surface drainage, Lagunita diverting ditch [Negative# 23-4], Undated (Box 8)
    - History and English building, rear view [Negative# 23-5 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Surface drainage, outlet of east quad drain [Negative# 23-6 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Surface drainage, outlet of combined Alvarado-Lasuen diverting drain and east quad drain [Negative# 23-8 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Surface drainage, outlet from New Gymnasium [Negative# 23-9 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Surface drainage, outlet across Pine Ave. near faculty field club house [Negative# 23-10 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Surface drainage, outlet of west quad, chemistry & museum [Negative# 23-11 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Surface drainage, outlet from center of quad at foot of oval [Negative# 23-12 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Original envelope listing for set 23 (Box 8)
    - Quad, corner building [Negative# 24-1 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Quad buildings [Negative# 24-2 ], Undated (Box 8)
    - Inner quad, staircase [Negative# 24-3 ], Undated (Box 8)